{
    "questions": {
        "question_1": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 6, 
                "b": -1, 
                "c": 1, 
                "d": -23, 
                "e": 32
            }],
            "question": "22 - (10 + 13)",
            "question_id": 1,
            "correct_choice": -1,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Intermediate",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"
        },

        "question_2": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 1, 
                "b": 0.071428571, 
                "c": 43.5, 
                "d": 0.54, 
                "e": 3.125
            }],
            "question": "7 / (8 + 5)",
            "question_id": 2,
            "correct_choice": 0.54,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Intermediate",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"

            
        },

        "question_3": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 24, 
                "b": 32, 
                "c": 15, 
                "d": 8, 
                "e": 6
            }],
            "question": "2 * 4",
            "question_id": 3,
            "correct_choice": 8,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Beginner",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"
            
        },

        "question_4": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 4, 
                "b": 12, 
                "c": 6, 
                "d": 60, 
                "e": 45
            }],
            "question": "9 * 5",
            "question_id": 4,
            "correct_choice": 45,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Beginner",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool"

            
        },

        "question_5": { 
            "choices": [{
                "a": 4, 
                "b": 6, 
                "c": 3, 
                "d": 12, 
                "e": 5
            }],
            "question": "30/6",
            "question_id": 5,
            "correct_choice": 5,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Beginner",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"

        },
        "question_6": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 35, 
                "b": 6, 
                "c": 15, 
                "d": 0, 
                "e": 14
            }],
            "question": "11 - 5",
            "question_id": 6,
            "correct_choice": 6,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Beginner",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"

            
        },

        "question_7": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 12, 
                "b": 20, 
                "c": 0, 
                "d": 39, 
                "e": 15
            }],
            "question": "2 - (2 - 12)",
            "question_id": 7,
            "correct_choice": 12,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Intermediate",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"


        },

        "question_8": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 14, 
                "b": 20, 
                "c": 28, 
                "d": 96, 
                "e": 182
            }],
            "question": "5 * 4",
            "question_id": 8,
            "correct_choice": 20,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Beginner",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"


            
        },

        "question_9": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 55, 
                "b": 44, 
                "c": 32, 
                "d": 69, 
                "e": 50
            }],
            "question": "1 x 2 + 6 x 8",
            "question_id": 9,
            "correct_choice": 50,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Advanced ",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "Bool"


        },

        "question_10": {
            "choices": [{
                "a": 60, 
                "b": 12, 
                "c": 108, 
                "d": 160, 
                "e": 6
            }],
            "question": "(4 - 1) * (3 - 1)",
            "question_id": 10,
            "correct_choice": 6,
            "user_answer_choice": "char",
            "confidence_score": "integer",
            "difficulty": "Advanced",
            "category": "Arithmetic",
            "startTime": "time_value",
            "endTime": "time_value",
            "session_time": "time_value",
            "saved_for_tutor": "Bool",
            "problem_completion": "True"

        }
    }
}
